

# MARCIN WRZOŚ

JUNIOR FRONTEND DEVELOPER

**PORTFOLIO** 

### PROFILE

I do not have commercial experience in IT, however I am working on my project with senior developers. I am a person who is characterized by a 'can-do' attitude and I am always trying to overcome the issue on my own. I am able to write responsive pages in React with Typescipt in line with the newest standards.

HOW TO REACH ME

Phone: +48 662 623 531 Email: marcin.wrzs@gmail.com

SKILLS

#### **Programming**

React, TypeScript, JavaScript, Context API, HTML, CSS (including SASS), bootstrap, webpack, github, SQL

#### **Achievements:**

Radio Luz: hosting weekly radio show called Ultradzwięki Toastmasters: practicing public speaking skills
Aiesec: marketing promotion of the event Dni Kariery
2017

**EDUCATION** 

#### Reskilled

Programming mentorship - work with senior developers on non commercial project in React + Typescript 2023 to present

# **Wrocław University of Economics**

Master of Finance and Accounting 2017 - 2019

#### **University of Wrocław**

Bachelor of National Security 2014 - 2017

# **PROJECTS**

#### **Foodie**

Project with recipes written in React and Typescript with hooks and react-router. Components have been styled by styled-components. Project is connected with an external API by Axios. Some functions are handled by Context API. The slider has been made by React Slick. Project has been published at this <a href="mailto:link.">link.</a> by Netlify.

# <u>Portfolio</u>

Project which depics my resume has been written in React with hooks and react-router. You are able to switch between Day and Night mode, open my resume in the Resume section or send an email by contact form which is supported by the service EmailJS.

## **Blackjack**

Project has been written in HTML, SCSS, Javascript with Object Oriented Programming standards and bundled in the Webpack.

WORK EXPERIENCE

# **Technical Lead, Broker Accreditation Analyst**

Axa XL | January 2023 to present

- · building and Improving process areas
- · coordinating process improvement initiatives

# **Analyst, Senior Financial Services Operations**

Factor Law | October 2020 to December 2022

- · improving the process by VBA,
- coordinating the work allocation across the Negotiator teams

# Security and Pricing Data Management Specialist

Credit Suisse | January 2020 to September 2020

· maintaining data of financial instruments and their prices

# **Data & Document Specialist**

UBS | February 2019 to October 2019

• providing customer service and support to Front Office

## Junior Representative, Reconciliation

BNY Mellon | January 2018 to February 2019

- data investigation using information from different vendors
- reconciliation against broker/custodian statements